The application exposes the "jThread" object to the script granting access to the following properties and methods:

Read-only properties:
   version        Returns the jThread version information (string)
   name           Returns the name of the jThread object (the host executable file).
   path           Returns the name of the directory containing the host executable.
   scriptName     Returns the file name of the currently running script.
   scriptPath     Returns the absolute path of the currently running script, without the script name.
   scriptFullName Returns the full path of the currently running script.
   arguments      Returns an Array with the arguments passed to the script
   isAsync        Boolean indicating if the script was called in async mode.
   stdOut         Returns string with the content of the stdOut stream
   stdErr         Returns string with the content of the stdErr stream

Read-write properties:
   currentFolder  Returns/sets the current active folder (string).

Functions:
   echo(string)   Outputs string to the standard output stream (stdOut) of the console.
   error(string)  Outputs string to the standard error stream (stdErr) of the console.
   input()        Waits for and returns keyboard input (return string). Throws error in async mode.
   sleep(time)    Suspends the running script for the specified amount of time (in milliseconds), freeing system resources.
                  Other scripts running asynchronously are not affected.
   runScript(scriptPath)
                  Loads and runs a script file in the current context, waiting for its execution.
                  No return value or parameters passed to the script, as it runs in the same context it shares
                  the Global scope and the jThread options.

Asynchronic functions:
   runScriptAsync(scriptPath, arguments...)
   evalAsync(scriptString, arguments...)
   functionAsync(function, arguments...)
                  Loads and runs a script file in a new context, returning immediately and running it in a new thread.
                  In the second alternative instead of loading from file, the script is received as a string.
				  In the third alternative the script is created from the body of the function.
                  The script runs in an independent context, not sharing the Global scope, and with no inter-script
                  communication. Information to the new script can be passed thru the jThread object of that script,
                  which is initialized with its arguments property cloning a serialized version of arguments... parameter.
                  No external or ActiveX or functions objects can be passed.
                  To avoid intermingling output, stdout and stderr of the new script will be buffered and output
                  in a block at the end of execution of the calling script.
                  
				  The function returns an object to monitor the state and return value of the script, with the
                  following members:
                     isRunning    Boolean indicating if the script is still running.
                     runTime      Time in seconds that the script has been running.
                     stdOut       Returns string with the content of the stdOut stream
                     stdErr       Returns string with the content of the stdErr stream
                     returnValue  An object with a copy of the return value of the script.
                                  Will be undefined while executing or if the script doesn't return a value.
                                  To return a value/object the script must place it in a variable a leave the variable as
                                  the las statement of the script. Example: var result=123; result; <end of script>
                                  When calling with functionAsync, it will be directly the return value of the function.
                                  As with parameters the object will be serialized and copied (no external objects).
                     exception    If the script finished due to an unhandled exception, the exception doesn't propagate to
                                  the calling script, but the corresponding exception object is copied here.
                     abort        Aborts the run of the script.  
