UNICODE TEST: áàâãäå
jThread - JavaScript Runtime Host with Multithreading v1.0
By Adrian Panella

Usage: jThread [host options] ScriptName.extension [script arguments]

Host Options:
   /?             Show extended help.
   /D             Enable script debugging.
   /P[:log file]  Activate profiling. If no log file supplied uses console output.
   /O:file        Redirects output to "file" instead of console.
   /E:file        Redirects errors to "file" instead of console.
   /T:minutes     Defines the maximum amount of minutes that the script can run before it is terminated.
                  Defaults to 0 (no time limit).
   /V             Verbose. Outputs log info on script start and finish.

The application generates output in UNICODE. To correctly see special characters in the console output, 
set de code page to the appropriate one. For example (Latin 1; Western European - ISO): chcp 28591
